Hi
In this video we are going to describe the RiskID application.
To start using RiskID you need get an user account. Let's do it.
Go to the end of user manual page and click Sign Up button.
Fill all field in form, submit it and log in.
Welcome to RiskID application.
This page show in left the Connection List. All connections were regrouped by their similarity.
There is three group easily identifiable by their different background color in the list.
Each connection in the list, from left to right, display information about their current label:
red circle to botnet, green circle to normal and yellow circle to unlabeled.
Next to it the index number of the connection in the list is displayed.
Followed appears a color representation for three feature in the connection:
periodicity (represented by orange), duration (represented by green) and size (represented by blue).
The intensity in the color represents the high or low presence of the characteristics in the connection.
If you clicked a connection in the list more information about that will be displayed in right section.
A bar chart display the connection symbol distribution, and a pie chart show connection periodicity feature.
When an unlabeled connection is selected the detailed block display both
the botnet and normal label connection more close to selected connection.
To select a label for unlabeled connection two buttons are in the bottom of each connection view.
Red button to botnet label and green button to normal label.
You can also filter connections in the list using some options on top.
Once your task over, you could download the resultant labeled dataset doing clicked on the "Save Labeling" button.
Good Luck !!!